http://www.automatic.com/termsofuse_english?intcmp=GN_FOOTER_NEW_WebsiteTerms

Help & Support
Radio Not Working?
Help! I can't hear all of the channels on my radio.
Support Center
Scripting must be enabled to use this site.
Search
Advanced Search
Search terms
Screen Reader users press enter to Limit by Category.
Limit by Category
This button does not work with screen readers. Please use the previous link instead. Select a category
Automatic Labs Update
Use the links below to find details about the shutdown of Automatic Labs and the discontinuation of its services.
General Information
Rebate Eligibility
Data and Privacy
General Information
Why has Automatic Labs discontinued its services?
Like many other companies in the United States, the COVID-19 pandemic has adversely impacted our business, and we have made the difficult decision to discontinue the Automatic connected car product, service and platform. All operations were shut down at 11:59 pm, PT, on May 28, 2020, including our automatic crash notification service.
My service has ended, what should I do with my Automatic adapter?
Please discard your adapter by following standard electronic recycling procedures. You do not need to send your adapter back to Automatic.
Rebate Eligibility
Am I eligible for a rebate for the Automatic service that I purchased?
In order to receive a rebate, you must have submitted your request by June 15, 2020.
How will the rebate be delivered?
If you applied for a rebate and were deemed eligible, your virtual Mastercard gift card was sent to the email address associated with your Automatic account before Aug 19 from the email address no-reply-automaticlabs@hawkmarketplace.com.  If you have not received your rebate, please check your spam or junk folders and if further assistance is needed please refer to https://www.myprepaidcenter.com/contact-us.
If you received an Automatic adapter from an Auto Dealership
If you purchased an Automatic adapter from your Auto Dealership, please contact your dealer directly. All participating dealers in the Automatic Dealer Program have been notified of the shutdown of Automatic and the discontinuation of service.
How do I activate my virtual Mastercard gift card?
Your virtual Mastercard gift card must be activated within 90 days months of the date you received it via email. Please follow the instructions in the email to activate your electronic Mastercard gift card. If you need help with activating your card, you may reach out to myprepaidcenter.com/contact-us.
When does my virtual Mastercard gift card expire?
Your virtual Mastercard gift card expires 6 months after issuance (date of email). Please visit www.myprepaidcenter.com/contact-us if you have any questions about your Mastercard gift card expiring.
I lost my virtual Mastercard gift card email
Please visit www.myprepaidcenter.com/contact-us for assistance with your virtual Mastercard gift card email.
Data and Privacy
As a former customer, what is Automatic doing with my personal information and driving data now that its services have been discontinued?
Your personal information and associated driving data will be permanently deleted from our records. Automatic may retain some data about you solely for legal, accounting or other corporate records. All other driving and personal data will either be made anonymous or deleted from our system.
Will Automatic sell my personal information and personalized driving data to third parties?
Automatic will not sell your personal information or driving data to any third party and your personal information and associated driving data will be permanently deleted. Automatic may retain some data about you solely for legal, accounting or other corporate records. All other driving and personal data will either be made anonymous or deleted from our system.
To submit a California Consumer Privacy Request, click here.
Was this answer helpful?
Yes
No
This is an answer feedback option for commenting on the helpfulness of the article only.
If you have additional questions or require assistance, please chat with our Listener Care Team.
Email *Required
Your Feedback *Required
Answers others found helpful
I'm already a subscriber. Do I get a discount on additional subscriptions?
I have two or more accounts. Can I combine them?
How do I add my new vehicle to my existing SiriusXM account? How do I transfer my existing paid subscription from my old vehicle to my new one?
How will I know when my trial subscription is ending?
I don't know my username or password to log in online or listen on the app. How do I reset my login?
If your radio is not receiving programming, send a refresh signal
Contact Us
Contact Us
If you can't find what you're looking for on our site, give us a call.
How Much Does It Cost?
Try SiriusXM for Free
Does My Car Already Have SiriusXM?
© 2019 Sirius XM Radio Inc.
